const e="english",o=200,a=49,t=[{id:1564,question:`Choose the word that is most nearly opposite in the meaning to the underlined word or group of words that will fill in the sentence.

At first, we found life in the town very <u>exciting</u> but soon it became rather _______`,option:{a:"tiring",b:"disturbing",c:"burdensome",d:"boring"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:`exciting: to bring out, stimulate or arouse interest

boring: causing boredom or unable to engage one's interest`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:1,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1565,question:`Select the option that best explain the information conveyed in the sentence

The man's Achilles' heel is women ________`,option:{a:"His weakness is women",b:"His strength is women",c:" He fights women",d:"He respects women"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"The phase 'Achilles' heel' means a small problem or weakness in a person or system that can result in failure. The phrase has it origin traced to the legend of Achilles, which tells the talk of Achilles, how he was dipped into the river by his mother, That is in order to make him invulnerable. His heel wasn't covered by the water and he was later killed by a narrow wound to his heel.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:2,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1566,question:`Choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options below

Constitution`,option:{a:"CON—sti—tu—tion",b:"con—STI—tu—tion",c:"con—sti—TU—tion",d:"con—sti—tu—TION"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"Constitution'  is stressed on the third syllable as seen in option C",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:3,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1567,question:`Choose the option that has the same consonant as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined

cla<u>sh</u>`,option:{a:"sharp",b:"cheap",c:"leisure",d:"school"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"Option A sharp has the same consonant at the beginning of the word",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:4,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1568,question:`Choose the option that has the same consonant as the one represented by the letter(s) underlined

<u>wh</u>o`,option:{a:"vehicle",b:"khaki",c:"rhyme",d:"hammer"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"Option D has the same consonant sound at the beginning of the word 'hammer' ",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:5,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1569,question:`Choose the option to which the given sentence relates

My Boss has an amiable DISPOSITION`,option:{a:"Does your boss have an amiable disposition",b:"Does my boss have an unfriendly disposition",c:"Does my colleague have an amiable disposition?",d:"Does my boss have an amiable complexion?"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"Still going by the rule when answering questions on emphatic stress, the option that doesn't have the emphasized word. In this case 'DISPOSITION' is the emphasized word on the only option without it is option D",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:6,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1570,question:`Choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options below

palatable`,option:{a:" PAL—a—ta—ble",b:"pal—A—ta—ble",c:" pal—a—TA—ble",d:" pal—a—ta—BLE"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:`Some words are made up of a root  and a suffix:

dangerous   =    root –> danger  +  ous –<  suffix
commercial   =    root –> commerc(e)  + al –<  suffix

In some words with suffixes, the stress stays on the same syllable as in the root. Compare:

‘danger and: ‘dangerous

In other words, the suffix changes the stressed syllable. Compare:

‘commerce and: com‘mercial

Suffixes which don’t usually change the stress pattern in the root word include (however they maybe some exceptions.) -able, -age, -al, -er, -ful, -less, -ness, -ous and -fy. For example:

comfort – ‘comfortable
per‘cent – per’centage
`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:7,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1571,question:`Choose the interpretation that you consider most appropriate for each sentence. 

Despite their newness on the job, the workers were remunerated rather handsomely. This means that _________?`,option:{a:"the salaries were poor",b:"those paid were handsome in appearance",c:" the salaries were attractive",d:"workers were paid by handsome accountants"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"The word 'remunerate' as used in the sentence means paid for services rendered or work done, while the word 'handsomely' means to a large degree, substantially and also connotes attractiveness",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:8,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1572,question:`Choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

The chairman is <i>Parsimonious</i>`,option:{a:"Avaricious",b:"thrifty",c:"generous",d:"accustomed"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`The word <i>Parsimonious</i> means very unwilling to spend money or use resources. On the other hand 'Generous is the opposite', meaning to give more of something especially money
From the above meaning of each words of option, generous best describes the opposite of parsimonious, as every other option is synonymous to parsimonious`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:9,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1573,question:`Choose the interpretation that you consider most appropriate for each sentence.

Now that Michael has become rich, Nancy has begun to make much of him. This means __________`,option:{a:"now values Michael",b:" now gets a lot of money from Michael",c:"only recently married Michael",d:"no longer wants to leave Michael"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"Make much of means to give much attention to someone or something or to treat very well ",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:10,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1574,question:`Choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

This event was a <i>watershed</i> in the company`,option:{a:"landmark",b:"blot",c:"publicity",d:"stain"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"The question has the word <i>watershed</i> italicized. The word means an event or perfect marking a turning point in a situation. It is synonymous to the word landmark which means an event or discovering marking an important stage or turning point in something",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:11,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1575,question:`choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

Snakes and ladders always______me happy these days`,option:{a:"makes",b:"make",c:"made",d:"making"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:`The correct option is option A (makes). This is so because singular nouns just like 'snakes and ladders'  are always followed by a singular verb and  'makes' is a singular verb. Recall one of the rules of concords says that, if the subject is singular, the verb should be singular and if the subject is plural, the verb should also be plural.

To better understand this, 'snakes and ladders' as used in this context refers to a game and not independent words. Hence, it will be followed by a singular verb. 

 A singular verb is a word that shows or explains what the subject has done, or what is being done, or what will be done. It is always used with a singular subject in a sentence.

In this regards, 'makes' explains what 'snakes and ladders' as a game does to the speaker.

Note that adverbs do not change the verb tense 

 `,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:12,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1576,question:`Choose the word that best completes the following sentence. 

I really like working in that office: I find the — very friendly`,option:{a:"condition",b:"atmosphere",c:"air",d:"situation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"Means the pervading tone or mood of a place, situation, or creative work.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:13,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1577,question:`Choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word

The delegates found it better to resort to <u>consultation</u> rather than __________`,option:{a:"conflict",b:"confrontation",c:"reconciliation",d:"consent"},section:"",image:"",answer:" b",solution:`Consultation ; the action or process of formally consulting or discussing. example: "they improved standards in consultation with consumer representatives"

synonyms: discussion, dialogue, discourse, debate, negotiation, conference, deliberation
 

confrontation; a hostile or argumentative situation or meeting between opposing parties.example "a confrontation with the legislature"

synonyms: conflict, clash, brush, fight, battle, contest, encounter, head-to-head, face-off, engagement, tangle, skirmish, collision, meeting, duel, incident, 
 `,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:14,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1578,question:`Choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

The delegates were given_____`,option:{a:" a two hour break",b:"a two-hour break",c:"a two-hours break",d:"a two hours break"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"When the article 'a' is used to introduce a time session it implies that you are making a singular form of what is actually plural. Generally, one should hyphenate two or more words when they come before a noun they modify and act as a single idea.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:15,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1579,question:`Choose the option nearest to the statement

My brother's drunkenness often got on my nerves. This means`,option:{a:"disgraced him",b:"made him ill",c:"made me angry",d:"offended me"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"To get on someone nerves means to irritate or annoy someone",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:16,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1580,question:`From the options given, Choose the option that is opposite in meaning to the underlined word.

This house which was <u>sealed</u> off years ago has now been —`,option:{a:"re-opened",b:"rebuilt",c:"re-roofed",d:"restored"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"Sealed off means to prevent people from entering a building",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:17,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1581,question:`Choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options. The stressed are written in capital letters

Judiciary`,option:{a:"judiCIAry",b:"judiciaRY",c:"JUdiciary",d:"juDIciary"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"|ju|DI|cia|ry|",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:18,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1582,question:`From the options, choose the word opposite in meaning to the underlined word

He is quite an <u>outspoken</u> young man but his father is_____?`,option:{a:"humorous",b:"sober",c:"taciturn",d:"silent"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`Outspoken: frank in stating one's opinions, especially if they are shocking or controversial. to be direct and open in speech and expression. 

synonyms: forthright · direct · candid · frank · straightforward · honest · open · straight · straight from the shoulder · plain · plain-spoken · vociferous · vocal · explicit · point-blank ·

 taciturn: (of a person) reserved or uncommunicative in speech; saying little.

"after such gatherings she would be taciturn and morose"

synonyms: untalkative · uncommunicative · reticent · unforthcoming · quiet · unresponsive · secretive · silent · tight-lipped · close-mouthed · mute · dumb · inarticulate · reserved

 `,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:19,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1583,question:`From the options, choose the word nearest in meaning to the underline word

By working hard, Benjamin <u>outshone</u> his elder brother instead of being ________`,option:{a:"overshadowed",b:"defeated",c:"demoted",d:"submerged"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:`outshine: shine more brightly than.

tower above and cast a shadow over. 

synonyms: surpass, be superior to, overshadow, eclipse, outclass, dwarf, tower above/over, put in the shade, upstage, put to shame, excel, exceed
overshadow: tower above and cast a shadow over. example "an enormous oak tree stood overshadowing the cottage"

synonyms: shade · darken · conceal · obscure · block out ·`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:20,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1584,question:`Choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

The students received a mild <i>reproof</i> from the teacher`,option:{a:"exhortation",b:"opposition",c:"commendation",d:"appropriation"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`This answer was chosen because it is opposite to the word italicized in the question; reproof which means an expression of criticism, blame.
From the above meaning of the other options, it is obvious that non-fits for the opposite of the word 'reproof'.

Commendation means an official or a formal praise`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:21,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1585,question:`Choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

Aisha <i>impelled</i> to the party`,option:{a:"compelled",b:"accompained",c:"authority",d:"finance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"The words 'impel and compel' are synonymous impel means drive, force or urge someone to do something while compel means force or oblige someone to do something.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:22,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1586,question:"When you ____ an opponent's point in a debate, you must do so politely",option:{a:"refute",b:"rebuke",c:"reject",d:"refuse"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"When you refute you prove a statement or theory to be wrong or false",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:23,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1587,question:`Choose the options that have the same consonant as the ones represented by the letter(s) underlined

lei<u>s</u>ure`,option:{a:"sure",b:"ledger",c:"treasure",d:"judge"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"Leisure has the same consonant sound as in treasure",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:24,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1588,question:`Choose the most appropriate stress pattern from the options. 

The stressed are written in capital letters
departmental`,option:{a:"DEpartmental",b:"dePARTmental",c:"departMENtal",d:"departmenTAL"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"de|part|MEN|tal",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:25,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1589,question:`choose the option opposite in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

They come here on bootless <i>errand</i>`,option:{a:"worthwhile",b:"vain",c:"delusive",d:"intended"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:`The word bootless means ineffectual, useless of a task or undertaking, while the answer worthwhile means worth the time, effort spent
Bootless explains that the errand was useless while worthwhile explains it was the effort, which is also synonymous to the word useful`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:26,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1590,question:`Choose the option to which the given sentence relates

Aderonke STATED she had a right to her privacy`,option:{a:"Did Omowunmi state she had a right to her privacy?",b:"Did Aderonke lament she had a right to her privacy?",c:"Did Aderonke state she had a right to her openness?",d:"did Aderonke state she had a right to his privacy"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"Stated' has been emphasized in the question, therefore Option B is the answer because the verb lament contradicts the emphasized word as used in the question",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:27,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1591,question:`Select the option that best explain the information conveyed in the sentence

The painting was beautifully faked`,option:{a:"The painting was a good deceptive replica",b:"The painting was well-framed and displayed",c:"The painting was deceptively decorated",d:"The painting was carefully designed"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"The painting being beautifully faced could also be described as a good deceptive replica, which means there is almost no difference in the fake painting and the original.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:28,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1592,question:`Choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

The crops the farmer planted will be ____ in three months time.`,option:{a:"sold",b:"weeded",c:"uprooted",d:"harvested"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"Contextually, 'harvested' is the most appropriate answer",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:29,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1593,question:`Choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

Garba acquiesced______their decision`,option:{a:"for",b:"on",c:"in",d:"by"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"The preposition 'in' is used with the verb 'Acquiesce'",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:30,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1594,question:`Select the option that best explain the information conveyed in the sentence

The letter was being written by the principal`,option:{a:" The letter had been written by the principal",b:"The principal was writing the letter",c:"The principal wanted to write the letter",d:"The principal wrote the letter"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"When the word 'being' is used in past continuous tense, as it is in the above question, it means the action is happening or was happening before, in a continuous manner, just like in the answer, the principal was writing the letter",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:31,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1595,question:`Select the option that best explain the information conveyed in the sentence

Advising Olu to break his bad habit is like knocking your head against a brick wall`,option:{a:" It is making a fool of you",b:"It is trying the impossible",c:"It is making him your enemy",d:"It is asking him to beat you"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:`This means trying the impossible.
The idiomatic expression 'knocking your hand against a brick wall' means to attempt continuously and fruitlessly to accomplish a task or achieve a goal that is or seem ultimately hopeless, more like it is impossible.`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:32,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1596,question:`Choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

_____a good boy, he was given a prize`,option:{a:"To being",b:"Been",c:"Being",d:"To been"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:'"Being" can be used as a gerund, a verb that functions as a noun. It becomes part of the subject sentence.',examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:33,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1597,question:`Choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

The children received gifts from <i>doting</i> parents`,option:{a:"nagging",b:"loving",c:"humble",d:"Docile"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"<i>Doting</i> is characterized by giving love and affection.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:34,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1598,question:`Fill in the Gap

The press will no longer be free when the new government starts to ------— newspapers`,option:{a:"censure",b:"edit",c:"publish",d:"censor"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"To officially suppress an unacceptable part of a book, film, news, etc.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:35,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1599,question:`Choose the best option that best completes the gap(s)

The_____event takes place every two years`,option:{a:"bienial",b:"biannual",c:"biennial",d:"biannal"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`Biannual occurring twice a year. this means an event that is celebrated two times in a year.  while 

Biennial means an event/occassion that takes place every two years. occuring once in every two years.

 `,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:36,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1600,question:`Fill in the Gap

Mr Collins does not allow his name to be published in connection with the philanthropy because he _____ publicity`,option:{a:"wields",b:"lacks",c:"detests",d:"defines"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:'Detest" best completes the sentence because the context tells us that Mr Collins does not like his name to publicized',examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:37,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1601,question:"The first time Paul met Ngozi, her beauty caught his eye. This means that _________",option:{a:" Ngozi admired Paul",b:"Paul recognized Ngozi.",c:"Ngozi attracted Paul.",d:"Paul surprised Ngozi"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"This means that Ngozi's beauty attracted Paul. In other words, Ngozi attracted Paul.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:38,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1602,question:`From the words lettered A to D, choose the word that has the same consonant sound(s)

Strange`,option:{a:"vague",b:"mirage",c:"logic",d:"legume"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`the ''ge'' in ''strange'' is the same consonant sound as the ''g'' in logic

strange is pronounced as  [streɪn(d)ʒ]

 `,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:39,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1603,question:"The government has decided to freeze student's grants. This means that government intends to",option:{a:"reduce grants meant for students",b:"resume paying grants to students",c:"make students repay the grants",d:"stop paying grants to students"},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"Freeze student's grants mean to stop giving grants to students",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:40,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1604,question:`Choose the option nearest in meaning to the word or phrase in italics

This case is within the <i>jurisdiction</i> of the council`,option:{a:"record",b:"prohibition",c:"authority",d:"finance"},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"<i>Jurisdiction</i>' the italicized word in the question means the official power to make legal decision and judgement while authority, the answer, is synonymous in that it means the power or right to give orders, make decisions",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:41,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1605,question:`Choose the option opposite in meaning to the word underlined

One of the twins was as <u>daring</u> as the other was ______`,option:{a:"morose",b:"timid",c:"secretive",d:"rational"},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:`Daring as used in this context, means to be bold or brave.
From the given options, B (timid) is the opposite in meaning to the word 'daring'.

Timid means Lack of boldness.`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:42,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1606,question:"Suleiman's reason for becoming a Muslim in the novel is because Islam brings sense of ______?",option:{a:" radicalism and aggression",b:"boldness and awareness",c:"kindness and truthfulness",d:"purpose and discipline"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"In chapter 30, Suleiman was resolute about tracing his roots and finally finding his identity amongst his people in Africa and in the religion, Islam",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:43,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1607,question:"Tayo opted to remain in Nigeria because he had a duty to serve his",option:{a:"students",b:"wife",c:"friends",d:"brothers"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"In chapter 24, Tayo mentioned his student as one major reason why he wasn't open to the demand from his wife, Miriam, to leave the country",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:44,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1608,question:'In the Novel "Independence" Tayo wrote a biography of ______?',option:{a:"Arthur Richardson",b:"Lord Lugard",c:"Obafemi Awolowo",d:"Nnamdi Azikiwe"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"In chapter 27, Tayo's biography of Lord Lugard became his new success",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:45,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1609,question:`In the book "Independence" Tayo's uncle, Kayode, wanted to study Engineering in _______?`,option:{a:"Britain",b:"U.S.A",c:"France",d:"Germany"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"In chapter sixteen, Tayo's uncle, Kayode, revealed to him that he was considering studying engineering at the Insitute du Petrole in France",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:46,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1610,question:'In the book "Independence" Wearing woolens, lamb cardigans, extra socks, gloves and Balliol scarf signified that Tayo was _______?',option:{a:"Cold",b:"Going to a party",c:"sick",d:"walking in the rain"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"Clothings, gloves, cardigans and extra socks are outfits worn during winter when the temperature is low, cold",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:47,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1611,question:'In the novel "Independence" Tayo lied to Vanassa that Christine was his ______?',option:{a:"sister",b:"niece",c:"aunt",d:"cousin"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"In chapter Nine, Tayo was showing Vanessa his collection of photographs when Christines popped out and then he lied about her being his cousin.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:48,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:1612,question:"According to Tayo the two major problems of Nigeria were",option:{a:"tribalism and religion",b:"politics and culture",c:"bribery and corruption",d:"greed and mismanagement"},section:"This question is based on S. L. Manyika's INDEPENDENCE",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"Chapter Twenty-one (21) of the book gave a narrative about how Tayo had been writing about the problems of Nigeria and how he believed that greed and mismanagement were the root causes of the problems.",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2017",questionNub:49,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],n={subject:e,status:200,total:49,data:t};export{t as data,n as default,o as status,e as subject,a as total};
